The UK is on every traveller's go-to list, but after the Brexit vote, with the pound dropping to historic lows, a trip to Britain is even more timely.
英国在全世界游客的必去清单上，但是，在英国脱欧公投后，随着英镑汇率降至历史低点，此时去英国游玩变得更加合时宜了。
The summer is a great time to be in Britain.
夏天是去英国的好时节。
The British Museum, the Natural History Museum, the Tate Gallery are all a must-see for everybody who comes to the country, but there's also a lot of interesting things to do for those who love the outdoors.
大英博物馆、自然历史博物馆、泰特美术馆对于每一个来到这个国家的人来说都是必看之处，但是对于那些喜欢户外活动的人来说，也有很多有趣的事情可以做。
The Notting Hill Carnival changes the face of the famous London borough in the last weekend of August.
诺丁山狂欢节在八月的最后一个周末改变了伦敦这个著名行政区的面貌。
It's the largest street festival in Europe.
这是欧洲最大的街头节日。
First held in 1964, it's a celebration of Caribbean culture but now includes Brazilians, Africans, Europeans and anybody else who likes to dress colourfully and feels the urge to dance to the sound of a beat.
它于1964年首次举办，原本是对加勒比文化的庆祝活动，但现在也包括巴西人、非洲人、欧洲人以及任何喜欢穿着色彩鲜艳的衣服，并且有随着节奏起舞冲动的人。
With its popularity growing it's estimated that 50,000 performers will take part in the parade, attracting more than 1 million people over the weekend.
随着它越来越受欢迎，据估计会有5万名表演者参加游行，在周末吸引超过100万人。
Outside the capital there's also plenty to do.
在首都之外也有很多可做的事情。
Early in August there's the Robin Hood Festival in Sherwood Forest Country Park, Nottinghamshire.
八月初，在诺丁汉郡的舍伍德森林郊野公园有罗宾汉节。
The legendary characters of books and movies - Robin Hood and the evil Sheriff of Nottingham - can be found there amid jousting tournaments and comedy acts.
书籍和电影中传奇的人物——罗宾汉和邪恶的诺丁汉郡长——会出现在那里的骑士比武比赛和喜剧表演中。
For those into nature, there's always the forest to enjoy.
对于那些热爱大自然的人来说，那里总有森林可供欣赏。
In mid-August, in Bristol, a city about 200km from London, the sky is filled with colour during its annual balloon fiesta.
八月中旬，在距离伦敦约200公里的布里斯托尔，在其一年一度的热气球狂欢节期间，天空中满是色彩。
If the weather is good, more than 100 hot air balloons rise up from the Fiesta's site in Ashton Court.
如果天气好的话，会有100多个热气球从阿什顿宫的狂欢节场地升空。
Britain is full of traditions and sometimes just stopping at a country pub for a beer or having cream tea in a small tea room can make a moment special.
英国充满了传统，有时候，仅仅是在乡村酒吧停下来喝杯啤酒，或者在小茶室里喝英式奶油茶点，就能让那一刻变得特别。
Just be careful where you end up, though.
不过，要小心你最终去的地方。
Coaches full of sightseers went to the small village of Kiddlington early this month.
本月初，满载观光客的大巴车来到了基德灵顿这个小村庄。
As the visitors were taking pictures of the houses and entering private gardens, the locals were taking pictures of them.
当游客们在给房子拍照并进入私人花园时，当地人也给他们拍照。
To this day, nobody knows what the tourists were doing there.
直到今天，也没人知道那些游客在那里做什么。
Always be sure where you are, and learn enough English to ask for directions.
一定要清楚自己在哪里，并且要学足够的英语来问路。
Have a nice holiday!
祝你度过一个愉快的假期！